(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2 Extra Episode=
Xingxu.
Have you finished everything?
I'm all done.
Let's start eating.
I've tried it.
Come on.
Chefs.
This is
ridiculous.
I'll give you a hand.
- I can't cook Sichuan dishes either.
- I'll help you out.
You know
I'm the best at helping out.
- I can help out too.
- Who knows how to make Sichuan food?
So many ingredients.
Chicken breast.
Chicken breast is out.
I don't know how to cook it.
Didn't you say
you could make it super delicious?
No.
How do you make Sichuan food with this?
This is beef, right?
Judging by the grain, it should be.
Looks like it.
What's up, everyone?
I can do the cutting.
I'll do anything you ask.
I'll do the chopping.
What are you going to do?
I don't know how to make Sichuan food.
Here's what I'm thinking.
I'll help out.
Jingfei and I
will handle
all the chili peppers.
(Chili manager on duty)
Because
- every Sichuan dish
- Is this a good idea?
has chili peppers.
- So for every dish,
we'll be in charge of adding the chilies
and doubanjiang.
Only 30% of Sichuan dishes are spicy.
The other 70% are not spicy at all.
Today, I'm going to make
(Just playing it by ear)
a non-spicy Sichuan dish.
Come on.
Let's start cooking.
I'll make Twice-cooked Pork.
Mapo Tofu is easy to cook.
Mapo Tofu is simple.
Boiled Spicy Beef.
Mapo Tofu.
Twice-cooked Pork.
Okay.
How about this?
You make one dish, I make one dish,
and you two make one together.
Okay.
He is good at cooking.
He is good at eating.
Yes. He is a good cook.
He can cook.
He can do it.
The braised pork belly
he made last time
was incredible.
What should we make first?
When it comes to Sichuan cooking,
I can only give you
a zero.
Just make that rice wine braised lamb.
I can do rice wine braised pork belly.
If... Yes.
No lamb on hand. Anything is fine.
(Signature rice wine reserved)
The key is the rice wine.
Scallion Braised Tofu.
There's hot pot base here.
Yes, here it is.
Shredded potatoes,
and mushrooms.
It's not hard at all.
Add some doubanjiang or hot pot base,
stir-fry it up,
and whatever you're cooking
will taste good.
(Just that simple)
Are you that particular?
Well, it's like...
It feels like a Master Chef
looking down on me,
thinking, "Can you even cook like that?"
That's cheating.
It's quick.
I want to eat.
Young ginger.
How about making Stir-fried Beef?
Okay.
Young ginger, celery...
Sure.
Scallions,
chili peppers,
beef.
All here.
Let's make Stir-fried Beef first.
I'll go with your call.
(Stir-fried Beef Confirmed)
Now I only need
you guys to do one thing.
Help me
slice some beef, okay?
Knife skills are crucial for this.
(Trusting us with this crucial job?)
If we mess up the slicing,
it'll turn into stir-fried beef chunks.
It's okay.
Could you guys cut
some celery segments for me?
Sure.
And cilantro sections.
Okay.
Just these two.
- Got it.
- Okay.
We need a vegetarian dish, right?
(Volunteering)
I'll make smashed cucumber salad.
Smashed cucumber salad, okay.
I'll do my prep work.
Prepping.
Bird's-eye chilies.
Ground pork.
Okay.
(Beef is ready)
Here we go, cooking time.
We have to cook a meal
at the end of every season.
Yeah.
Yuning, can I have some?
There's plenty.
I want this one.
So big.
Take this one.
That's such a big piece.
It's okay if you don't use it all,
I'll use the rest.
(Take the required portion)
(Slice the beef)
(Stack the beef slices)
(Cut beef into strips)
Time to buckle down on knife work.
Fresh meat is actually
the hardest to slice.
(Going over meat-slicing tips)
Frozen meat
is easier to slice.
- Freeze it all the way hard, right?
- Frozen solid is easier to cut.
They can be cut more neatly.
(Learned something new)
That's all from experience.
Yes.
I'm making Stir-fried Beef.
(Cut beef into strips)
Give me some garlic.
Give me some ginger.
(Handy helper online)
Alright, garlic is here.
I'll take this job.
Move over.
Okay.
Enough?
That's enough.
Put it there.
(Volunteering to pitch in)
I'll heat up the pan for you.
Bro.
Help me...
I need to boil this first.
Give it one cut for me.
What kind of cut do you want?
What size should I make it?
Slices.
But I need to boil it first.
Cold water...
Start with cold water in the pot.
- You slice it after it's cooked, right?
- Yes.
This amount is good.
Enough.
- Okay.
- That's enough.
(Add scallions and Sichuan peppercorns
to remove the raw-meat smell)
(Wait for it to blanch until cooked)
Garlic.
No garlic.
Here.
All peeled.
How are you going to cook this?
Boil it in water.
I'll pour the water for you.
It's fine.
I want to make this later.
It'll take a long time to cook, right?
No.
15 minutes is enough.
I'm pouring oil for you.
Wait a second.
Let me think.
I can't make it too spicy.
I'll switch
the bird's-eye chilies to...
Less bird's-eye chilies,
more green peppers.
Can't make it too spicy.
Just cook it
however tastes best.
I've got a lot to chop.
I could quickly
finish cutting everything for you,
then you can stir-fry right away.
But mine needs to boil for 20 minutes.
So what are you going to do?
Just chop the garlic
and that...
How should I cut the garlic?
Minced garlic, right?
You've got a lot of prep to do, right?
Yeah, I've got quite a bit.
It's a bit of a hassle.
(Mince the garlic)
(Chop the scallions)
(Chop some bird's-eye chilies)
(Marinate the beef)
(Season with pepper powder and salt)
(Add garlic, egg white,
and bird's-eye chilies)
(Mix everything thoroughly
and set it aside to marinate)
(Shred ginger, shred celery, chop green
bell peppers, chop sweet bell peppers)
(Prep work is done)
Guys, let's start stir-frying beef!
I'm pouring in the oil?
- Pour in some oil.
- Okay.
Pour...
Pour a bit more.
(Stir-fry beef until color changes)
(Dish out and set aside)
(Add ginger, garlic, chilies,
add doubanjiang, add soybean paste)
(Add the beef back in)
Okay.
Take it away.
Here.
(Add chicken bouillon,
add sugar, add vinegar)
(Add celery)
(Stir-fry over high heat)
It's pretty much done.
Add some oyster sauce.
And we'll finish it off.
Let me toss it around.
Let me show off a bit.
Look.
Wait.
Look, I can do it.
Alright.
Give it a couple tosses.
Dish it out.
(Wang Yuwen: Stir-fried Beef)
Have a taste.
It's a bit hot.
Blow on it.
Taste it.
How's the seasoning? Is it salty?
It's great.
It's perfect for my taste.
(Thumbs up +2)
It's good.
Tasty?
Good.
Have a taste, Yuning.
Done already?
Stir-fried Beef, right?
Thanks.
Just right.
Not overcooked at all.
Perfect.
Is it good?
It's good.
Delicious.
What are you going to do?
I want to whip up some garlic sauce.
Doing it like this is a bit...
I don't have the tools.
This is the only way.
No.
Clear out the bowl first.
Smash the garlic, then chop it fine.
(Isn't someone already mincing garlic?)
What are you doing?
Mince some for me, while you're at it.
Thanks.
- I don't need that much.
- No.
Mince some for me.
I have no tools over there.
Nice.
You're clearly practiced at this.
If I did this, garlic bits would
go flying right to the crew.
You'd make the basin
and the pot clatter.
Right.
Let me do this.
(Garlic mincing complete)
Oh, no.
I'm totally clueless
when it comes to chili-based dishes.
What are bird's-eye chilies?
Here.
Bird's-eye chilies are super spicy.
- This one, right?
- Yeah.
These are bird's-eye chilies.
(Staring intently)
Is it relaxing?
He looks like...
He looks like a gorilla in the zoo.
He can stare intently
at one simple task.
Mind your own business.
(Waiting in line)
I'm waiting for the cutting board to be free.
Actually, you don't even need it
for the cucumber.
Don't you want to cut it into strips?
I don't need to.
Then let's make smashed cucumber salad,
okay?
Okay, smashed cucumber salad works.
After you peeled it, this cucumber
looks completely stunted.
I went a bit too hard with the peeler.
What seasonings do we need?
Vinegar.
Garlic...
Minced garlic.
Garlic.
Chili peppers.
- Chili peppers.
- Cilantro.
Cilantro.
Sesame oil.
- Salt, MSG.
- Then just toss you in too.
Leave this wok to me.
- Okay.
- Okay?
No problem.
(Add ginger and garlic to saute)
This...
Bro.
(Can this hold all the tofu?)
Why didn't you just bring a wine cup?
- What do you mean?
- He wants me
to put this huge chunk of tofu
into this bowl.
Be careful!
It's going to splatter. Move back!
(Stir-fry the chicken over high heat)
Quite the commotion.
That's just what I thought.
(Add salt and rock sugar)
(Add chicken bouillon, light and dark
soy sauce to enhance flavor)
(Taste and adjust seasoning)
This looks so good.
Cola Chicken?
You think anything dark-colored
tastes good.
I just realized.
That's true.
- Wang Yuwen.
- This really looks delicious.
After spending time with her,
I've noticed she thinks
anything dark-colored
tastes good.
(Secret weapon ready)
(Pour in rice wine)
Guys,
here comes
the dark cuisine.
Just add some chili peppers,
and it becomes Sichuan cuisine.
For this dish...
What's it called?
Whatever!
(Going with the flow)
(Looking for a tasting judge)
Lean down and smell this dish.
(Let me smell it)
What can you smell from this?
I can smell a hint of wine.
- And a hint of
- It's alright.
chicken.
Let it boil up.
Help me chop some cilantro
into fine bits for me.
Okay.
Yeah, cilantro bits work too.
I'm doing Scallion Braised Tofu.
Cut it into normal-sized pieces.
Normal size.
You need to explain clearly to him.
Hope he doesn't mince it into mush.
Look, Wang Yuwen.
Is this okay?
Good, Fei.
A bit small, but it's fine.
Can we use it for that now?
That?
No, I need to do
the smashed cucumber salad.
- You seem to be loving all this work.
- Absolutely.
You're kind of in the way.
You know?
Should I smash the cucumber
like this first? Right?
How to smash the cucumber?
Cucumber...
I don't know.
Shouldn't you...
Okay, good.
(Where there's a will, there's a way)
If all else fails, just ask AI.
As long as we have something to eat,
it's fine.
You got cucumber bits everywhere
on the floor.
Truly smashed cucumber.
(Smash the cucumber and chop it up)
(Plate it and set aside)
Do you think adding some sesame oil
would make it tasty?
Of course.
Add some scallions.
These scallions are so small.
Are these scallions?
- Yes.
- Are these really scallions?
Separate the white parts
from the greens.
Can't separate them.
If they can't come apart,
just keep them together.
Add a little garlic
and fry it together.
Actually, Scallion Braised Tofu
only needs scallions and tofu.
Add some minced meat.
(Pan-fry tofu until golden on each side)
(Dish out and set aside)
(Add minced meat)
(Stir-fry minced meat
until it turns brown)
(Add scallions)
(Add tofu)
(Drizzle the special sauce)
(Wang Yuwen: Scallion Braised Tofu)
(Focus on prepping ingredients)
You're back.
How about we do this one first?
Sure.
Yuning is almost done
with all the prep work.
I just need to finish cutting this.
Then we can...
What step are you on?
Once I'm done cutting,
let's just start stir-frying.
The tofu looks good.
(Passing the secret mission)
Do you feel like hot pot?
Yes.
Well,
there is something
we can't let Nai find out.
Our mission
is to cook
all the ingredients
thoroughly
and eat them.
Let's get this done first.
- Quick, you take that...
- I've turned on the stove.
Are you...
You take over. I'm done cutting.
You do the cooking now.
I'll put those ingredients in the pot.
- What do you think?
- Okay.
I'll go first.
I'll...
I'll take you there. It's fine.
I'll take you there first,
then come right back.
- Where's the restroom around here?
- It's over there.
(Studying intently)
Ginger, garlic,
douban,
and fermented black beans.
This step is especially crucial.
What are you guys doing?
Mapo Tofu.
Are you using the wok right now?
This one.
No, go ahead.
Is the water boiling?
No.
I haven't lit the stove yet.
(Add salt for base flavor)
Add a spoonful of salt first.
(Add dark soy sauce for color)
Half a spoonful of dark soy sauce.
(Blanch to remove odor)
Once the water boils, put in the tofu.
Blanch for one minute.
(Drain well and take out)
Pass me the knife.
I need to chop something.
This is ginger?
Ginger.
Why does it look like scallion?
That's the top part of the ginger.
(Heat the wok, then pour in oil)
(Coat the wok)
(Add minced meat)
It's fine.
Don't panic.
So slow.
- It's fine, don't panic.
- Good. Take it easy.
(Stir-fry until browned)
Remove odor.
(Add ginger and cooking wine)
Light soy sauce.
Right?
Add a bit of dark soy sauce.
Give it some color.
Color it.
Teach it a lesson.
Stir-fry a bit, then take it out.
Take it out.
Success.
Here.
Cold oil, right?
Not hot yet.
Just leave it like this for now.
Heat it up.
Save that for later.
Put this in first.
- Add the minced garlic?
- Yes.
Saute it.
- Add the paste.
- Yes.
Okay.
Good, stir-fry it.
You have to keep stirring this.
It burns really easily.
Just keep stirring it, right?
Yes.
Keep going.
Keep stirring?
Yeah, stir-fry it.
Fry out the red chili oil
and it'll smell amazing.
Otherwise, it'll taste raw.
Yeah, the more you stir-fry,
the more fragrant it gets.
Awesome.
I feel like...
Just looking at this, I can tell
it's going to be delicious.
It smells so good
what you're cooking.
Just take a whiff. It's incredible.
(Corners of mouth curling up)
Okay, come on.
(Add water)
Just add this and it's done, right?
Yeah.
(Add tofu)
Slide it in.
Okay.
It's got that perfect vibe.
Incredible.
Good.
Almost.
I've learned two dishes from you.
Not really.
Braised Tofu and Braised Eggplant.
That's true.
No, you learned this all by yourself.
(Add starch slurry)
Stir it, right?
Stir it.
(Add chopped scallions)
How's the look?
How is it?
It looks
really appetizing.
Really appetizing.
Okay, turn off the heat and dish it out.
(Chen Xingxu and Lin Yi: Mapo Tofu)
I'm going to get started.
(Guokui with Twice-Cooked Pork)
(Prepping ingredients)
(Smash, chop, plate)
Cut a small Guokui.
(Cut Guokui into pieces and set aside)
(Curious)
What are you making? Roujiamo?
No, Guokui.
Guokui?
Yeah, Guokui with Twice-Cooked Pork.
(Heat wok, pour in oil, add Guokui)
Deep-fry the Guokui first.
(Fry until golden brown)
(Dish out and set aside)
Is this pork belly?
This is the hind-quarter meat.
Perfect for twice-cooked pork.
(Blanch pork and rinse in cold water)
Rinse it.
I'm going to slice the meat.
(Slice the meat)
Jun, where did you get this pork belly?
Looks really good.
- Want some? I'll give you half.
- If you've got any leftovers,
- I don't need this much.
- give me the rest.
Okay.
Okay, I'll save these for Wen.
I'm getting ready to stir-fry.
(Add meat and stir-fry)
High heat stir-fry.
(Excited)
(Add salt, scallion, ginger,
fermented black beans, and doubanjiang)
(Add garlic sprouts, add Guokui)
(Plate it)
Done.
This is fantastic.
(Gong Jun:
Guokui with Twice-Cooked Pork)
(Slice the beef)
Slicing the meat?
Yeah.
- Need to slice it.
- Okay.
(Slice beef into strips)
Okay.
- Awesome.
- Impressive.
(Add starch)
(Pepper powder)
(Salt)
(Marinate)
(Shred green and red bell peppers)
(Shred celery)
(Shred young ginger)
How many dishes have you made, Yuning?
I haven't even finished one.
(Shredded Beef with Young Ginger,
Start stir-frying)
(Heat wok, pour in oil,
add marinated beef once oil is hot)
Cool.
That's such a big pot.
Nice.
Yeah.
Stir-fried Beef.
(Add vegetables and secret sauce)
Professional.
A big portion of Stir-fried Beef.
Let me take a bite.
Not done yet.
Because the heat is a bit slow.
Take a bite.
Let me take a bite.
I should grab chopsticks,
just like that "Just one bite" meme.
(Come back later)
Just one bite.
The kitten one, right?
Yeah, just one bite.
Smells great.
Pretty good.
Taste it.
Quick.
Taste it, see if it's salty.
Hurry up.
Yuwen, your turn for a bite.
(Here I come)
Jun.
Hi, let me take a bite.
Not bad.
Is it good?
Good.
Come on.
A bit hot.
It's good.
But I think
you can add some sugar.
Add a little sugar to boost the umami.
Or a few drops of vinegar works too.
(Liu Yuning:
Shredded Beef with Young Ginger)
Stir-fry bullfrog.
Never done it before.
Okay.
- Bullfrog is delicious.
- First time?
First time.
I've never even used doubanjiang before.
- Anyway, marinate it first.
- Bullfrog is delicious.
(Add starch and marinate)
(Add Sichuan peppercorns)
(Add chili sections)
(Add marinated meat)
(Add ginger pieces, season with salt,
pour in some water)
This must be delicious.
I can already smell it.
(Add chopped scallions)
This smells
amazing.
Guys, it's my first time making this.
Pardon my cooking.
(Chen He: Chick-frog)
(Sneaky vibe hot pot session,
Total peak sneaky vibe)
Boil the water first.
Turn on the heat.
(I'm back with my teammates)
Over here?
Right.
I've already got it cooking.
You've got it cooking, right?
Let's move these ingredients
down below first.
It's too visible up here.
It's not boiling yet.
- Put the things in first.
- Put it all in.
All in.
Wait.
It's hot.
It's fine.
Put the ingredients in.
No.
I'm adding the ingredients.
Where's the hot pot base?
- Is it boiling?
- Not yet.
Can't eat it yet.
Go back first.
(I'll head out first)
When it boils, I'll...
Wave at me.
I'm sweating already.
It's boiling so slowly.
(Anxious)
Why isn't it boiling yet?
Not ready yet.
It's not boiling yet. Almost.
It just started bubbling.
Almost.
(Starting to bubble)
See? Almost boiling.
Can we start dipping?
I think it's almost ready.
We can put them in now.
- It's already bubbling.
- I think it's about ready.
Keep an eye on it for me.
I'm watching.
(Can't bear to watch)
You don't need to be so gentle.
Just pour it right in.
What else?
Just these, right?
There's another plate over there.
More?
Let me handle it. You head back first.
Eat.
And then?
(Got all the ingredients in the pot)
Don't move.
What do you mean?
It hasn't boiled.
We have to eat all of this?
(Standing by)
- We'll each take some.
- What else?
Just this one pot.
Everything's dumped in.
It hasn't boiled yet.
How long has this been cooking?
Not long,
just put them in.
This only needs a few seconds,
then it's ready to eat.
But there's way too much stuff in here.
It's so hot.
(Having hot pot is no easy feat)
Almost.
It's about to...
Let's eat.
(Happy)
What are you two doing?
Eat.
We can't all come over, can we?
- Honglei.
- It's ready.
It's good to go.
Pick out some greens.
But we've got to
finish all of this.
All of it?
All of us here.
No dipping sauce?
There is sauce. Which one do you want?
It's actually pretty good.
(Thumbs up)
I'm going to get the others.
Delicious.
Have some minced garlic.
Nice.
I'll have some too.
Look.
Okay.
(Smells delicious)
I'm leaving.
Grab another pair of chopsticks for Nai.
There's not much left to eat.
How is it?
Is it good?
I'll get some
for him.
Who?
Naiwen.
Bye.
Bye, Honglei.
It's my turn to eat, right?
A bowl of Nai's smashed cucumber salad.
The hot pot is great.
Paired with this half-bowl
of refreshing cucumbers from Nai.
(Not good)
No way.
It's insanely spicy.
Way too spicy.
Nice.
Let the others take over.
(Total sneaky vibe)
Who put the chicken feet in?
You scared me.
Nothing to fear.
Are we really this bold?
What is in this pot?
(Curious)
All chicken feet.
Cheers.
Come on, cheers.
They're all tasting your dish.
Mapo Tofu.
So good.
This hot pot base is tasty.
What are you doing?
Squat down.
I'm even using...
I'm even eating out of a cup.
Grab me a little bit.
Take some of this.
- Okay.
- Here.
Have some enoki mushrooms.
Come on.
Meat.
Tasty.
Nothing left.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪That day,
we traveled together far away♪
♪In countless late nights,
we exchanged courage♪
♪Our fates have already intertwined♪
♪In each other's life trajectories♪
♪We leave behind
bonds like no other for a lifetime♪
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪Traveling around the earth♪
♪Tasting all the freshness♪
♪Having traveled all corners♪
♪We still stand shoulder to shoulder♪
♪I'm glad to have met you♪
♪We sing beautifully together♪
♪Even if we're scattered in the future♪
♪Thankfully we still share the same sky♪